<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
  <Series>
    <id>71663</id>
    <Actors>|Dan Castellaneta|Hank Azaria|Harry Shearer|Marcia Wallace|Julie Kavner|Yeardley Smith|Nancy Cartwright|</Actors>
    <Airs_DayOfWeek>Sunday</Airs_DayOfWeek>
    <Airs_Time>20:00</Airs_Time>
    <ContentRating>TV-PG</ContentRating>
    <FirstAired>1989-12-17</FirstAired>
    <Genre>|Animation|Comedy|</Genre>
    <IMDB_ID>tt0096697</IMDB_ID>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Network>FOX</Network>
    <NetworkID></NetworkID>
    <Overview>Originally created by cartoonist Matt Groening, &quot;Our Favorite Family,&quot; has graced the small screen in one form or another for over 20 years. The Simpson family first appeared on television as the subjects of interstitial &quot;shorts&quot; on The Tracey Ullman Show in April of 1987. The Simpsons remained a staple on The Tracey Ullman Show for three seasons until they premiered in their own half-hour series, on December 17, 1989. With the help of Jim Brooks and Sam Simon, Matt Groening's cartoon family turned into an instant success.

Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.

Currently in its 23st season, The Simpsons has piled up close to 500 episodes, 27 Emmy Awards, a handful of music albums, countless endorsements and merchandise, and even made the jump to the silver screen in the summer of 2007 with The Simpsons Movie. And according to Matt Groening, &quot;There is no end in sight.&quot;</Overview>
    <Rating>9.1</Rating>
    <RatingCount>387</RatingCount>
    <Runtime>25</Runtime>
    <SeriesID>146</SeriesID>
    <SeriesName>The Simpsons</SeriesName>
    <Status>Continuing</Status>
    <added></added>
    <addedBy></addedBy>
    <banner>graphical/71663-g13.jpg</banner>
    <fanart>fanart/original/71663-10.jpg</fanart>
    <lastupdated>1349118559</lastupdated>
    <poster>posters/71663-9.jpg</poster>
    <zap2it_id>EP00018693</zap2it_id>
  </Series>
</Data>
