<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
  <Series>
    <id>94551</id>
    <Actors>|Lauren Graham|Bonnie Bedelia|Craig T. Nelson|Dax Shepard|Monica Potter|Erika Christensen|Joy Bryant|Tyree Brown|Mae Whitman|Sarah Ramos|Savannah Paige Rae|Peter Krause|Sam Jaeger|Miles Heizer|Max Burkholder|Xolo Maridueña|</Actors>
    <Airs_DayOfWeek>Tuesday</Airs_DayOfWeek>
    <Airs_Time>10:00 PM</Airs_Time>
    <ContentRating>TV-PG</ContentRating>
    <FirstAired>2010-03-02</FirstAired>
    <Genre>|Drama|</Genre>
    <IMDB_ID>tt1416765</IMDB_ID>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Network>NBC</Network>
    <NetworkID></NetworkID>
    <Overview>From writer/executive producer Jason Katims (Friday Night Lights) -- this contemporary re-imagining of the blockbuster film depicts the colorful and imperfect Braverman family -- four grown siblings sharing the headaches, heartaches and joy of being parents. The star-studded cast includes Peter Krause, Lauren Graham, Craig T. Nelson, Dax Shepard, Bonnie Bedelia, Monica Potter, Erika Christensen and Sarah Ramos. When Sarah Braverman (Graham, Gilmore Girls), a financially strapped single mother, returns home to her parents and siblings in Berkeley, Calif. after packing up her Fresno apartment and uprooting her two inconvenienced kids, Amber (Mae Whitman) and Drew (Miles Heizer), she is greeted by her opinionated father, Zeek (Nelson), and strong mother, Camille (Bedelia) who are privately dealing with their own marital issues. As Sarah is reunited with her siblings -- sister, Julia (Christensen), and brothers Crosby (Shepard) and Adam (Krause) -- all struggling with issues of their own, it's clear that the Braverman reunion is just what they need to face the everyday challenges of modern family life.</Overview>
    <Rating>8.6</Rating>
    <RatingCount>25</RatingCount>
    <Runtime>60</Runtime>
    <SeriesID>76680</SeriesID>
    <SeriesName>Parenthood (2010)</SeriesName>
    <Status>Continuing</Status>
    <added>2009-05-16 12:42:03</added>
    <addedBy>5664</addedBy>
    <banner>graphical/94551-g3.jpg</banner>
    <fanart>fanart/original/94551-1.jpg</fanart>
    <lastupdated>1358230899</lastupdated>
    <poster>posters/94551-2.jpg</poster>
    <zap2it_id>SH01154163</zap2it_id>
  </Series>
</Data>
