<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
  <Series>
    <id>273690</id>
    <Actors>|Matt Ryan|Angélica Celaya|Lucy Griffiths|Harold Perrineau|Charles Halford|</Actors>
    <Airs_DayOfWeek>Friday</Airs_DayOfWeek>
    <Airs_Time>10:00 p.m.</Airs_Time>
    <ContentRating></ContentRating>
    <FirstAired>2014-10-24</FirstAired>
    <Genre>|Action|Adventure|Fantasy|Horror|Thriller|</Genre>
    <IMDB_ID>tt3489184</IMDB_ID>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Network>NBC</Network>
    <NetworkID></NetworkID>
    <Overview>Based on the wildly popular  DC Comics series Hellblazer. The series focuses on seasoned demon hunter and master of the occult John Constantine, a dark magician who is struggling with his past sins as he tries to protect humanity from a gathering supernatural threat, John Constantine specializes in giving hell… hell. 
Armed with a ferocious knowledge of the dark arts and his wickedly naughty wit, he fights the good fight or at least he did. With his soul already damned to hell, he’s decided to leave his do-gooder life behind, but when demons target Liv, the daughter of one of Constantine’s oldest friends, he’s reluctantly thrust back into the fray and he’ll do whatever it takes to save her. Before long, it’s revealed that Liv’s second sight, an ability to see the worlds behind our world and predict Supernatural occurrences is a threat to a mysterious new evil that’s rising in the shadows. Now it’s not just Liv who needs protection, the angels are starting get worried too. Together, Constantine and Liv must use her power and his skills to travel the country, find the demons that threaten there world and send them back where they belong. After that, who knows… maybe there’s hope for him and his soul after all.</Overview>
    <Rating>6.0</Rating>
    <RatingCount>2</RatingCount>
    <Runtime>60</Runtime>
    <SeriesID>193994</SeriesID>
    <SeriesName>Constantine</SeriesName>
    <Status>Continuing</Status>
    <added>2013-09-29 06:35:06</added>
    <addedBy>394890</addedBy>
    <banner>graphical/273690-g2.jpg</banner>
    <fanart>fanart/original/273690-1.jpg</fanart>
    <lastupdated>1405855973</lastupdated>
    <poster>posters/273690-2.jpg</poster>
    <tms_wanted_old>0</tms_wanted_old>
    <zap2it_id></zap2it_id>
  </Series>
</Data>
