<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Data>
  <Series>
    <id>95461</id>
    <Actors>|Alex O'Loughlin|Katherine Moennig|Daniel Henney|Justina Machado|Alfre Woodard|Christopher J. Hanke|</Actors>
    <Airs_DayOfWeek>Sunday</Airs_DayOfWeek>
    <Airs_Time>9 pm</Airs_Time>
    <ContentRating></ContentRating>
    <FirstAired>2009-10-04</FirstAired>
    <Genre>|Drama|</Genre>
    <IMDB_ID>tt1440346</IMDB_ID>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Network>CBS</Network>
    <NetworkID></NetworkID>
    <Overview>Three Rivers is a medical drama that goes inside the emotionally complex lives of organ donors, the recipients and the surgeons at the preeminent transplant hospital in the country where every moment counts. However, dealing with donor families in their darkest hour and managing the fears and concerns of apprehensive recipients takes much more than just a sharp scalpel. Leading the elite team is Dr. Andy Yablonski (Alex O'Loughlin), the highly-skilled workaholic lead organ transplant surgeon, whose good-natured personality and sarcastic wit makes him popular with his patients and colleagues. His colleagues include Dr. Miranda Foster (Katherine Moennig), a surgical fellow with a rebellious streak and fiery temper who strives to live up to her deceased father's excellent surgical reputation; Dr. David Lee (Daniel Henney), a womanizing surgical resident who's broken as many hearts as he's replaced; Ryan Abbott (Christopher J. Hanke), the inexperienced new transplant coordinator who arranges the intricately choreographed process of quickly and carefully transporting organs from donor to patient; Dr. Sophia Jordan (Julia Ormond, unaired pilot), the head of surgery and a dedicated medical professional; and Pam Acosta (Justina Machado), Andy's no-nonsense operating assistant and best friend. In this high stakes arena, in which every case is a race against the clock, these tenacious surgeons and medical professionals are the last hope for their patients.</Overview>
    <Rating>7.0</Rating>
    <RatingCount>1</RatingCount>
    <Runtime>60</Runtime>
    <SeriesID></SeriesID>
    <SeriesName>Three Rivers</SeriesName>
    <Status>Ended</Status>
    <added>2009-05-22 03:04:16</added>
    <addedBy>5664</addedBy>
    <banner>graphical/95461-g.jpg</banner>
    <fanart>fanart/original/95461-2.jpg</fanart>
    <lastupdated>1344456700</lastupdated>
    <poster>posters/95461-1.jpg</poster>
    <zap2it_id></zap2it_id>
  </Series>
</Data>
